{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597447318","data":{"timestamp":" 947597447318"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597447373","data":{"timestamp":" 947597447372"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" 981c2c04-e773-426e-96b7-4e7d5e6fcbb9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_63"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani alikutana na msichana mmoja mwembamba na mrembo mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597821642","data":{"timestamp":" 947597821641"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" 981c2c04-e773-426e-96b7-4e7d5e6fcbb9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_63"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Njiani alikutana na msichana mmoja mwembamba na mrembo mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597821732","data":{"timestamp":" 947597821732"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" 90059ed0-b65e-441a-ac89-cb80ea36cbd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa aligeuka na kukimbia na hadi leo hajawahi kuonekana tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597847117","data":{"timestamp":" 947597847117"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b00f4dd3-674f-43f8-b462-39495c98dfe2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dau"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DAU"," userResponse":" DAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597855979","data":{"timestamp":" 947597855978"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b00f4dd3-674f-43f8-b462-39495c98dfe2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dau"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DAU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597857582","data":{"timestamp":" 947597857581"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b00f4dd3-674f-43f8-b462-39495c98dfe2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dereva"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEREVA"," userResponse":" DEREVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597866379","data":{"timestamp":" 947597866379"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b00f4dd3-674f-43f8-b462-39495c98dfe2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dereva"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEREVA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597868024","data":{"timestamp":" 947597868024"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b00f4dd3-674f-43f8-b462-39495c98dfe2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DOGO"," userResponse":" DOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597872147","data":{"timestamp":" 947597872147"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b00f4dd3-674f-43f8-b462-39495c98dfe2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DOGO"," userResponse":" DOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597873773","data":{"timestamp":" 947597873773"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b00f4dd3-674f-43f8-b462-39495c98dfe2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dudu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUDU"," userResponse":" DUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597876129","data":{"timestamp":" 947597876128"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b00f4dd3-674f-43f8-b462-39495c98dfe2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dudu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUDU"," userResponse":" DUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597877769","data":{"timestamp":" 947597877768"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b00f4dd3-674f-43f8-b462-39495c98dfe2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" debe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEBE"," userResponse":" DEBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597883533","data":{"timestamp":" 947597883533"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b00f4dd3-674f-43f8-b462-39495c98dfe2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" debe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEBE"," userResponse":" DEBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597885174","data":{"timestamp":" 947597885173"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b00f4dd3-674f-43f8-b462-39495c98dfe2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dobi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DOBI"," userResponse":" DOBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597887417","data":{"timestamp":" 947597887417"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b00f4dd3-674f-43f8-b462-39495c98dfe2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dobi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DOBI"," userResponse":" DOBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597889049","data":{"timestamp":" 947597889049"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b00f4dd3-674f-43f8-b462-39495c98dfe2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597892778","data":{"timestamp":" 947597892778"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b00f4dd3-674f-43f8-b462-39495c98dfe2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597894398","data":{"timestamp":" 947597894397"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b00f4dd3-674f-43f8-b462-39495c98dfe2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" duma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUMA"," userResponse":" DUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597901403","data":{"timestamp":" 947597901402"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b00f4dd3-674f-43f8-b462-39495c98dfe2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" duma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597903443","data":{"timestamp":" 947597903442"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b00f4dd3-674f-43f8-b462-39495c98dfe2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" duma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597903688","data":{"timestamp":" 947597903688"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b00f4dd3-674f-43f8-b462-39495c98dfe2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" duma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597965186","data":{"timestamp":" 947597965185"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b00f4dd3-674f-43f8-b462-39495c98dfe2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" duma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597974736","data":{"timestamp":" 947597974736"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" 92d3b483-ae73-4560-8d01-19b584e8c774"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_d-u-i"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597978639","data":{"timestamp":" 947597978638"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" 92d3b483-ae73-4560-8d01-19b584e8c774"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_h-z-d"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597982780","data":{"timestamp":" 947597982780"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" 92d3b483-ae73-4560-8d01-19b584e8c774"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_v-d-g"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597986478","data":{"timestamp":" 947597986478"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" 92d3b483-ae73-4560-8d01-19b584e8c774"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_y-t-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597991567","data":{"timestamp":" 947597991567"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" 92d3b483-ae73-4560-8d01-19b584e8c774"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_d-g-i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597995630","data":{"timestamp":" 947597995630"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" 92d3b483-ae73-4560-8d01-19b584e8c774"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_d-o-t"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947597999722","data":{"timestamp":" 947597999722"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" 92d3b483-ae73-4560-8d01-19b584e8c774"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_z-d-a"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598004110","data":{"timestamp":" 947598004110"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" 92d3b483-ae73-4560-8d01-19b584e8c774"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_d-h-ch"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598008328","data":{"timestamp":" 947598008328"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" 92d3b483-ae73-4560-8d01-19b584e8c774"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_s-f-d"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598012530","data":{"timestamp":" 947598012530"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" 92d3b483-ae73-4560-8d01-19b584e8c774"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_o-d-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598018305","data":{"timestamp":" 947598018304"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" 92d3b483-ae73-4560-8d01-19b584e8c774"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_d_o-d-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598048090","data":{"timestamp":" 947598048090"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" deb91bbb-1768-4370-94fb-3ef0bbce31ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598071604","data":{"timestamp":" 947598071604"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" deb91bbb-1768-4370-94fb-3ef0bbce31ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598074355","data":{"timestamp":" 947598074355"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" deb91bbb-1768-4370-94fb-3ef0bbce31ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598097746","data":{"timestamp":" 947598097746"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" deb91bbb-1768-4370-94fb-3ef0bbce31ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598140673","data":{"timestamp":" 947598140673"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" deb91bbb-1768-4370-94fb-3ef0bbce31ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598143404","data":{"timestamp":" 947598143404"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" deb91bbb-1768-4370-94fb-3ef0bbce31ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598172727","data":{"timestamp":" 947598172726"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" deb91bbb-1768-4370-94fb-3ef0bbce31ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598172853","data":{"timestamp":" 947598172853"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" deb91bbb-1768-4370-94fb-3ef0bbce31ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUTHONI"," userResponse":" MUTHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.85","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598179485","data":{"timestamp":" 947598179484"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" deb91bbb-1768-4370-94fb-3ef0bbce31ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598261029","data":{"timestamp":" 947598261028"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" deb91bbb-1768-4370-94fb-3ef0bbce31ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598271565","data":{"timestamp":" 947598271564"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598274004","data":{"timestamp":" 947598274004"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598275606","data":{"timestamp":" 947598275605"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598278464","data":{"timestamp":" 947598278463"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598280091","data":{"timestamp":" 947598280089"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598282245","data":{"timestamp":" 947598282244"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598283845","data":{"timestamp":" 947598283845"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598291445","data":{"timestamp":" 947598291445"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598293063","data":{"timestamp":" 947598293062"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598295374","data":{"timestamp":" 947598295373"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598296960","data":{"timestamp":" 947598296960"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598300916","data":{"timestamp":" 947598300916"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598302499","data":{"timestamp":" 947598302498"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598305315","data":{"timestamp":" 947598305315"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598306884","data":{"timestamp":" 947598306883"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598309668","data":{"timestamp":" 947598309668"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598311255","data":{"timestamp":" 947598311255"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598315174","data":{"timestamp":" 947598315173"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598316788","data":{"timestamp":" 947598316788"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598320230","data":{"timestamp":" 947598320230"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598321844","data":{"timestamp":" 947598321844"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598324622","data":{"timestamp":" 947598324622"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598326219","data":{"timestamp":" 947598326218"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598335619","data":{"timestamp":" 947598335619"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598337235","data":{"timestamp":" 947598337234"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598340326","data":{"timestamp":" 947598340326"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598341926","data":{"timestamp":" 947598341926"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598344925","data":{"timestamp":" 947598344925"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598346485","data":{"timestamp":" 947598346485"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598348761","data":{"timestamp":" 947598348761"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598350313","data":{"timestamp":" 947598350313"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598353619","data":{"timestamp":" 947598353619"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598355179","data":{"timestamp":" 947598355179"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598358550","data":{"timestamp":" 947598358550"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598360097","data":{"timestamp":" 947598360097"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598364923","data":{"timestamp":" 947598364922"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598366477","data":{"timestamp":" 947598366477"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598369694","data":{"timestamp":" 947598369694"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598371258","data":{"timestamp":" 947598371258"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598374798","data":{"timestamp":" 947598374798"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598376346","data":{"timestamp":" 947598376346"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598378768","data":{"timestamp":" 947598378768"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598380327","data":{"timestamp":" 947598380327"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598383204","data":{"timestamp":" 947598383204"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598384752","data":{"timestamp":" 947598384752"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598388048","data":{"timestamp":" 947598388048"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598389602","data":{"timestamp":" 947598389601"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598392014","data":{"timestamp":" 947598392014"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598394023","data":{"timestamp":" 947598394022"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947598394088","data":{"timestamp":" 947598394088"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947600241681","data":{"timestamp":" 947600241680"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" b66c4e76-4107-4a01-8adf-83903bb5cb4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947600241753","data":{"timestamp":" 947600241753"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_163007"," gameId":" 84d1cdec-b9d3-49bd-8c7b-3fd4cdb13147"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}